"No pain no gain!"
"没有付出就没有收获！"
That's a mindset applied to many things – from working long hours when starting a new business, to studying hard for an important exam.
这是一种适用于许多事情的思维模式——从创业时长时间工作，到为重要考试而努力学习。
And gym culture often encourages people to push themselves to their limits, leading people to have an all or nothing attitude, where they feel they must either have an extremely tough fitness regime, or do nothing at all.
健身房文化常常鼓励人们将自己推到极限，导致人们有一种要么全力以赴要么一无所获的心态，他们觉得要么必须进行极其困难的健身计划，要么就什么都不做。
But what if it doesn't have to be this way?
但如果不用如此呢？
What if you can improve your fitness and wellbeing with minimal effort?
如果你可以用最少的努力来改善你的健康和福祉呢？
Meet the new trend gaining traction: zone zero exercise.
来认识一下正在获得关注的新趋势：零区运动。
Zone training is about your heart rate.
分区训练与心率有关。
For example, zone 1 exercise requires 50% of your maximum heart rate, up to zone 5 which is 100% effort.
例如，一区运动需要你最大心率的50%，而五区则是100%的努力。
Activities range from a dog walk or easy warm-up in zone 1, to a sprint up the stairs at zone 5.
活动的范围从一区的遛狗或轻松热身，到五区的冲刺上楼梯。
Think of zone zero as any kind of movement that keeps your heart rate below 50%.
把零区想象成任何让你的心率保持在50%以下的运动。
This could be a gentle stroll, a few stretches in between long stints of sitting at your desk, even gardening or light housework.
这可以是悠闲散步，在长时间久坐办公期间做几次伸展，甚至园艺或轻度的家务。
Terry Tateossian, a personal trainer and nutritionist, said that for many of her clients, "zone zero is the bridge between sedentary and sustainable".
私人教练兼营养师特里·塔泰奥西安说，对她的许多客户来说，"零区是久坐和可持续之间的桥梁"。
It is exercise that feels effortless.
这是一种感觉毫不费力的运动。
One major benefit of zone zero activity is accessibility.
零区活动的一个主要好处是易接近性。
For those unable to do high intensity workouts, such as those recovering from injury, light exercise may feel like a smaller mountain to climb.
对于那些无法进行高强度锻炼的人，比如正在从受伤中恢复的人，轻度运动可能感觉像爬一座更小的山峰。
And with this comes another benefit – consistency.
随之而来的是另一个好处——持续性。
A routine based on zone zero activity is easier to sustain, meaning the long-term benefits are easier to achieve.
基于零区活动的日常例行活动更容易维持，这意味着长期益处更容易实现。
A 2018 review of research, published in the International Journal of Behavioural Nutrition and Physical Activity, found that zone zero activity can support mental wellbeing, help regulate blood sugar and improve circulation.
2018年发表在《国际行为营养与体育活动杂志》上的一项研究综述发现，零区活动可以提升心理健康，帮助调节血糖，改善血液循环。
It can even lower the risk of cardiovascular disease.
它甚至可以降低心血管疾病的风险。
Of course, if you're gunning for a personal best, or wanting to significantly improve your fitness, you shouldn't stop at zone zero activities.
当然，如果你正努力争取个人最好成绩，或者想要显著提升你的体能，你不应该止步于零区活动。
You'll need to do challenging, high-intensity workouts to grow stronger.
你需要进行有挑战性的高强度锻炼才能变得更强。
But even top athletes must embrace gentle movement.
但即使是顶级运动员也必须接受温和的运动。
Endurance coach Stephanie Holbrook says, "it's often the missing piece that unlocks breakthrough performances because it facilitates genuine recovery."
耐力教练斯蒂芬妮·霍尔布鲁克说："这往往是解锁突破性表现所缺失的一环，因为它促进了真正的恢复。"
Maybe slowing down is the best way to move forward.
也许放慢速度才是取得进展的最佳方式。